<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Mimansa Jaiswal</title>
<link>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/index.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Personal notes</description>
<image>
<url>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/preview.png</url>
<title>Mimansa Jaiswal</title>
<link>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/index.html</link>
<height>92</height>
<width>144</width>
</image>
<generator>quarto-1.3.433</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>What is the easiest way to create AND maintain a personal academic website?</title>
  <link>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/personal_academic_website.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Another week of personal website debate on Twitter, another set of heavy compilation based suggestions to create and maintain a personal website. So, I decided to take a look at all the recent website builders and provide a set of recommendations. If you do not want to read this in entirety, my suggestions can be summarized below:</p>
<div class="callout callout-style-default callout-note callout-titled">
<div class="callout-header d-flex align-content-center">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-title-container flex-fill">
Summary of available website building options: sorted from most to least recommended. Use:
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container callout-body">
<p><em>This document only talks about the first 4 options.</em></p>
<ol type="1">
<li><p>Montaigne if you want the easiest option ever. (Apple Notes only, you can use icloud Apple Notes)</p></li>
<li><p>Notion to Astro, if you want to write in Notion, and are okay setting up github actions once for automatic deployment.</p></li>
<li><p>Decap CMS or Cloud Cannon if you want to host the static site elsewhere, but sync the content (editable in wysiwyg) with github.</p></li>
<li><p><a href="https://quarto.org/">Quarto</a> (how <a href="https://github.com/mimansajaiswal/mimansajaiswal.github.io">this website</a> is made) if you want heavy LaTeX support and the ability to embed runnable visualizations/code in your document.</p></li>
<li><p><a href="https://editable.website/">editable.website</a> if you want to edit the website easily, but are willing to spend time on the <a href="https://github.com/michael/editable-website#deployment-to-flyio">first setup on fly.io</a>.</p></li>
<li><p><a href="https://sites.google.com/">Google Sites</a> if you are okay with your data not being portable, but want a quick editing experience.</p></li>
<li><p>Use <a href="https://astro.build/">Astro</a> with <a href="https://getdarkmatter.dev/">Dark Matter</a> (ping on <a href="https://twitter.com/vadimdemedes/status/1681051391186329603">twitter</a> for access) if you are proficient with writing main page content in HTML, but want to write blog posts/collections in markdown. Suggested themes: <a href="https://github.com/satnaing/astro-paper">Astro Paper</a> and <a href="https://github.com/chrismwilliams/astro-theme-cactus">Astro Cactus</a>.</p></li>
<li><p>Use <a href="https://gohugo.io/">Hugo</a> or <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll</a> (for example <a href="https://github.com/adityatelange/hugo-PaperMod">Paper Mod</a>) if you trust yourself to keep up with the process required to maintain this website.</p></li>
</ol>
</div>
</div>
<section id="montaigne" class="level1">
<h1>Montaigne</h1>
<div class="callout callout-style-simple callout-note no-icon">
<div class="callout-body d-flex">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon no-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container">
<p><strong>Website</strong>: <a href="https://montaigne.io/">montaigne</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Website</strong>: <a href="https://mimansajaiswal.montaigne.io/">Demo Website Created Using Montaigne</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Content</strong>: <a href="https://www.icloud.com/notes/015MtzesWUvmeenWEvIgjN2-g#mimansajaiswal.montaigne">Apple Notes Folder Used To Create Demo Website</a></p>
<p><strong>Note</strong>: The developer has kindly suggested that they would be willing to a pay-what-you-want option for students who use montaigne and need to point it to a custom domain. Their pricing suggests it is $2/mo, but please contact them over Twitter or email for subsidized custom domain pricing.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>I knew about montaigne for around 4 months, but never gave it a serious look. Who wants a website made out of their Apple Notes, with no customization and not much to look at? Oh well, I was wrong!</p>
<section id="example-website" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="example-website">Example Website</h2>
<p><a href="https://mimansajaiswal.montaigne.io/">Here is the website</a> I made using montaigne. Man, it works! There is nothing missing in it, that I would need on a personal website! Sure, it does not have comments using giscus as I do, but who really needs that? Yes, the domain is hard to spell, but, the developer very kindly offered a pay what you want pricing for custom domains. Yes, you cannot host it on github, but the content is all in Apple Notes. The day montaigne goes down, you will still have all your content with you and be able to port it elsewhere.</p>
<p>If you want to figure out what the source notes requires or needs, I even made the folder of notes that I use to create the website public (<a href="https://www.icloud.com/notes/015MtzesWUvmeenWEvIgjN2-g#mimansajaiswal.montaigne">Link</a>).</p>
</section>
<section id="supported-content" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="supported-content">Supported Content</h2>
<p>What all can you do using Apple Notes? Well a ton! You can customize your menu, headers etc. You can use images, videos, embeds, headings that have anchors. Take a look <a href="https://mimansajaiswal.montaigne.io/research-notes/new-research-note">here</a>! Yes, the tags are clickable and filterable! You can do folders. It comes integrated with an RSS feed, quick links to your profiles in the footer, and a QR code to add on your research posters for someone to quick access your personal website.</p>
</section>
<section id="tldr" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="tldr">tl;dr</h2>
<p>Honestly, I cannot recommend this option enough. The domain would cost you a bit (maybe $10/year), if you go the custom domain route, but the ease of updating your website in a second beats any other options.</p>
</section>
</section>
<section id="notion-to-astro" class="level1">
<h1>Notion to Astro</h1>
<div class="callout callout-style-simple callout-note no-icon">
<div class="callout-body d-flex">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon no-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container">
<p><strong>Website</strong>: <a href="https://github.com/otoyo/astro-notion-blog">Original Github Source</a></p>
<p><strong>My Fork</strong>: <a href="https://github.com/mimansajaiswal/demo-astro-notion-blog">Modified Astro Notion Blog Github Source</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Website</strong>: <a href="https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/demo-astro-notion-blog/">Demo Website Using Astro Notion</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Content</strong>: <a href="https://template-collector-mj.notion.site/5e35b59e7a0447a78b7b793ab63250a0">Template To Create Demo Website</a></p>
<p><strong>Note</strong>: If you are okay with one time setup of github actions and github environment variables, this would be my recommended go to option. You can point it to a <code>username.github.io</code> domain or add a custom domain. You can deploy manually or on a cron schedule.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Many of us now write in Notion. Yes, github static pages exist, but they aren’t collaborative, they are a pain to edit, they aren’t visual enough, you cannot talk through comments (no, I do not want to read through issues for a blog post, thank you).</p>
<p>Notion to Astro solves all of that. It gives you a writing environment in Notion, but renders it as a website through Astro. It allows you for ample customization by customizing the astro files and the associated CSS unlike montaigne.</p>
<section id="example-website-1" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="example-website-1">Example Website</h2>
<p>The default notion to astro effort is rendering of a collection on the main page. The only problem with that structure is that most of us have an index file that is a list of things we do, and then a blog post. Many academic websites have no blog posts. So, I modified the template to suit the general style of academic websites. You can play around with it <a href="https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/demo-astro-notion-blog/">here</a>.</p>
<p>There are a few other additions too! I really loved the <a href="https://astro-theme-cactus.netlify.app/">Astro Cactus theme</a> and the search functionality it provides. So, I used their code for <a href="https://pagefind.app/">Pagefind</a> and integrated it into the original source code. If you are someone who is okay with editing JS files directly or proficient with Astro, you can find that theme <a href="https://github.com/chrismwilliams/astro-theme-cactus">here</a>. Another theme I will suggest for people who want to create in Astro rather than in Hugo/Jekyll is <a href="https://github.com/satnaing/astro-paper">Astro Paper</a>. Astro cactus did not have giscus. And I wanted giscus, because that is what I am using for my current websites, and I’ll explain my workflow in detail in the [#Quarto] section, but if everything aligns, I will happily switch to using this method. So, I integrated giscus based off this <a href="https://github.com/piero-vic/pierolescano.com">repo</a>.</p>
<p>Yes, this is a hacked together repo, because I understand code, but I do not have it in me to figure out how astro works. No, GPT4 did not help much with the understanding part of the equation.</p>
</section>
<section id="supported-content-1" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="supported-content-1">Supported Content</h2>
<p>Notion supports a ton of stuff, and so does the original repo from Otoyo. Here is the <a href="https://astro-notion-blog.pages.dev/posts/supported-blocks/">original page</a> of supported content. In comparison to montaigne, it supports a ton of extra blocks, just because it is based off Notion (Apple Notes is feature limited, not montaigne’s fault in this case). Specifically, as extras, it supports twitter embeds, link previews and bookmarks, code blocks with syntax highlights, synced blocks, toggles, files, callouts and highlights! What it is missing? Well, it does not support RSS feed or QR code and does not come with a supported footer section.</p>
</section>
<section id="tldr-1" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="tldr-1">tl;dr</h2>
<p>If you are comfortable with github at all, and are okay setting up actions and environment variables (and creating an integration key in Notion), I will suggest this option. It is a one time option, it never needs to be touched again in a code format, it requires no push and pull. And if you are worried about what happens when Notion goes down, you can export your content in .md files and host it elsewhere 5 years later. As I said, this document is meant for pseudo-owning your content and convenience/accessibility. It ain’t meant for “what happens when Notion no longer exists in 10 years, and my exports are not perfect”.</p>
</section>
</section>
<section id="decap-cms-or-cloud-cannon" class="level1">
<h1>Decap CMS or Cloud Cannon</h1>
<div class="callout callout-style-simple callout-note no-icon">
<div class="callout-body d-flex">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon no-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container">
<p><strong>Website</strong>: <a href="https://decapcms.org/">Decap CMS</a> or <a href="https://cloudcannon.com/">Cloud Cannon</a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</section>
<section id="quarto" class="level1">
<h1>Quarto</h1>
<div class="callout callout-style-simple callout-note no-icon">
<div class="callout-body d-flex">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon no-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container">
<p><strong>Website</strong>: <a href="https://quarto.org/">Quarto Official Website</a> and <a href="https://quarto.org/docs/websites/">Using Quarto for Creating Websites</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Website</strong>: <a href="mimansajaiswal.github.io">You are on it!</a></p>
<p><strong>Demo Source Code</strong>: <a href="https://github.com/mimansajaiswal/mimansajaiswal.github.io">Github Repo</a></p>
<p><strong>Note</strong>: If you are okay with editing your website completely in markdown online, or creating a mirrored local repo and using the visual editor for Quarto in VS Code, then pushing the changes to github, you will do fine with Quarto. You almost always do not need such a complicated website, and it requires a ton of CSS to make it look good (feel free to copy mine), but it works with YAML and that is immensely useful, especially for stuff like papers (<a href="https://github.com/mimansajaiswal/mimansajaiswal.github.io/blob/master/single_page/papers.yaml">example</a>) or experience (<a href="https://github.com/mimansajaiswal/mimansajaiswal.github.io/blob/master/about_me/experience.yaml">example</a>) that you just need to keep adding.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</section>
<section id="conclusion" class="level1">
<h1>Conclusion</h1>


</section>

<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>Tools</category>
  <category>Website</category>
  <category>Academia</category>
  <guid>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/personal_academic_website.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>What softwares do I actually use on my Mac as a software enthusiast?</title>
  <link>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/mac_softwares.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>On a daily basis, I use multiple apps and I prefer to put them together here. In general, I am always looking for better note-taking apps, and if you have any suggestions, I would love to know (trust me, I have tried 800 of them!). I will divide this into different categories of software I use, in case they are helpful for anyone.</p>
<!-- ::: callout-important
## Incomplete Post

This is incomplete and I will be filling it over the next few weeks.
::: -->
<p>For some context, I use a M1 Pro, Macbook Pro, with 16GB RAM and 512GB SSD. Some of these applications might not be great on 8GB RAM or 128GB SSD, so proceed with discretion.</p>
<section id="productivity-software" class="level1">
<h1>Productivity Software</h1>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>Communication</strong>: <a href="https://sparkmailapp.com/spark2">Spark Email 2</a> is my email client of choice rather than using the general Apple mail client. Why? Because it has the ability to remove Updates/Promotions/Forums from my main inbox that Apple mail does not. It also does basic Newsletters and Pins options for each email account, that Apple mail does not. To have all the DMs in one place, I use <a href="https://texts.com/">Texts</a>. If you do not have multiple accounts per app, you can also use <a href="https://www.beeper.com/">Beeper</a>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Tasks</strong>: I use <a href="https://todoist.com/">Todoist</a>. I have used 100 other apps, but I keep coming back to Todoist. With their quick capture being all bang based, nothing is easier for me to quick capture, schedule, rescheduled, completed. It syncs with Google Calendar. It works in collaboration mode. This is the only task tracker that has worked for me.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Terminal</strong>: <a href="https://www.warp.dev/">Warp</a> as terminal. I do not work with vim, so take my advice with a grain of salt. But I really like block based terminals. It also has a bang based AI mode. You can type <code>#</code> to ask it to provide the command that <code>converts all images in this folder and sub-folders to .webp and delete the original versions</code> and it will provide you with the command with templated tab-able arguments.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Sticky Notes</strong>: <a href="https://numi.app/">Numi</a> is the app I use for pasting on always on top notes. It is also great for calculations inside notes. It is extremely expensive, so probably get it on sale rather than anytime else, would be my recommendation.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Calendar and Timers</strong>: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dato/id1470584107">Dato</a> is for calendar and meetings. It shows the meeting time and current time across timezones, shows a monthly calendar, has an option to join a meeting from the menu bar. The reason I use it over <a href="https://www.mowglii.com/itsycal/">itsycal</a> is for its full screen notifications because I otherwise forget the meeting time or join a minute or two late. If you do not need that or timezones, itsycal is free and does everything else. I also use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/day-progress/id6450280202">Day Progress</a> because I am time-blind, but most people would not need it. I use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/red-hot-timer/id929960914">Timer RH</a> for always on top timers for timed tasks. It connects with the calendar as well, is pretty easy to set rather than using a Siri command (just drag the menu bar icon down to however long you need the timer to be).</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Note taking</strong>: I use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/aiko/id1672085276">Aiko</a> at the moment for transcription of my blabberings, <a href="https://app.tactiq.io/">Tactiq</a> for remote meetings, and <a href="https://otter.ai/">Otter</a> for in person meetings. For long form note taking, I use <a href="https://www.notion.so/">Notion</a> at the moment, but it is not necessarily my tool of choice, given its poor AI integration that would allow me to go from unstructured to structured content. It also lacks a calendar integration and spatial system, so I am always on a lookout for something different. Some other softwares I am exploring are <a href="https://tana.inc/">Tana</a> (better AI and API integration), <a href="https://capacities.io/">Capacities</a> (no collaboration), <a href="https://heptabase.com/">Heptabase</a> (no collaboration) and <a href="https://workspace.google.com/products/docs/">Google Workspace</a> (no block based editing but has newly added chips, task management, linking previews etc). I use <a href="https://www.goodnotes.com/">Goodnotes</a> or <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notes/id1110145109">Apple Notes</a> for handwritten note taking.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Reference management</strong>: I used to use <a href="https://paperpile.com/">Paperpile</a> but I shifted to using Notion for this purpose because I could not make use of the highlighted information. I use either <a href="https://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/">ar5iv</a> or <a href="https://papertohtml.org/">Paper To HTML</a> to snip papers into notion.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Whiteboarding</strong>: I use <a href="https://www.guga.co/">Guga</a> (new app, chinese support) or <a href="https://museapp.com/">Muse</a> (expensive but works really well, has a teams version). I tried <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/freeform/id6443742539">Freeform</a> and did not like it much. Guga also does not have desktop support which kinda hampers its usage on my end.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Reading</strong>: I use <a href="https://readwise.io/read">Reader from Readwise</a>, they allow you to annotate pdfs, videos webpages, add highlights, add notes to highlights etc. It is cheap for students; syncs highlights from everywhere to Notion and works reliably. The two other options are <a href="https://omnivore.app/">Omnivore</a> (open source and free) and <a href="https://hq.getmatter.com/">Matter</a> (better and more intuitive design but does not work with pdfs or videos). For podcasts, because apparently the information now also comes from podcasts, I use <a href="https://www.snipd.com/">Snipd</a>, which has headphone button based sniping, AI snip boundaries and snip summaries, and also syncs to Readwise or separately to Notion.</p></li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="creative-work" class="level1">
<h1>Creative Work</h1>
<p>I divide creative work into 2 parts, sometimes overlapping, creative work as an hobby, creative work for my research.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Flowcharts</strong>: <a href="https://whimsical.com/">Whimsical</a> and <a href="flowchart.fun">flowchart.fun</a>. Whimsical is great for making beautiful handmade flowcharts or making flowcharts easily using AI. Flowchart.fun provides a simple language to create flowcharts by just writing text.</li>
<li><strong>Screenshots</strong>: <a href="https://shottr.cc/">Shottr</a> allows to create annotated screenshots, blur parts of image on device. It also allows for rolling screenshots where if you capture an area it will auto scroll the webpage or any other document for you. Shottr is free and is extremely cheap for pro version (which is only needed for not getting pinged for updating after 30 days). I use <a href="https://pika.style/">pika</a> for pretty backgrounds around screenshots.</li>
<li><strong>Screen recordings</strong>: Explaining a coding process or a step-by-step guide on about how to do something, we often end up with full screen videos with tiny text. I use <a href="screen.studio">screen.studio</a> or <a href="https://screenrun.app/">screenrun</a> for automatic zoom ins into where I am clicking or typing. Screenrun can also do a short video from a screenshot if you want to say, oh, click here and then here and then here.</li>
<li><strong>Paper diagrams</strong>: <a href="draw.io">draw.io</a> for making neural network diagrams. There is unfortunately nothing that comes close. I cannot do TikZ, but if you can, more power to you!</li>
<li><strong>Drawing</strong>: I use <a href="https://procreate.com/">Procreate</a> or <a href="https://concepts.app/en/">Concepts</a>. Procreate allows for really intuitive drawing interface whereas concepts is vector based, and still allows for all the flair with layers, brushes, objects etc.</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="works-in-background" class="level1">
<h1>Works in Background</h1>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>Memory</strong>: <a href="Rewind.ai">Rewind.ai</a> has been a life-saver for me, it records everything on screen, and records laptop audio and mic if you choose to. It has two main things: search rewind and ask rewind. Search rewind is a simple keyword search over everything that has been stored. Ask rewind sends everything in those clips to OpenAI (possibly GPT3.5 16k) to create a summary and adds “screenshot” references.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Shortcuts</strong>: <a href="https://www.raycast.com/">Raycast</a> allows for doing so many things that I do not know how to describe it. It is local first and is free. It also has a pro subscription if you need its AI chat options (which comes with a student discount). The best way I have seen it described is Spotlight++ but I never used spotlight. You can use <code>⌘+Space</code> to do calculations, timezone conversions, unit conversions, quick word lookup, file search, screenshot search etc.</p>
<div class="callout callout-style-default callout-tip callout-titled">
<div class="callout-header d-flex align-content-center">
<div class="callout-icon-container">
<i class="callout-icon"></i>
</div>
<div class="callout-title-container flex-fill">
Amphetamine and Other Menu Bar Apps
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout-body-container callout-body">
<p>You can also remove the amphetamine software you have and use the menu bar coffee app that Raycast provides. It comes with many extensions, such as, hypersonic that can connect to any notion database of yours to show tasks, schedule them etc, all from <code>⌘+Space</code> or from your menu bar.</p>
<p>Another menu bar app that I use from Raycast is Text Shortcuts which allows you to select any task, and convert case, URL encode and decode, convert to markdown, find text statistics (word counter, character counter) etc.</p>
</div>
</div></li>
<li><p><strong>Camera</strong>: This is a small software, but I have cats, and I have messy hair. I use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/id1632827132">Camera Preview</a> a ton both for checking on myself and using the return key to click photos. <a href="https://handmirror.app/">Hand mirror</a> is the alternate option, but it cannot click photos.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Utilities</strong>: I use <a href="https://www.macbartender.com/">Bartender</a> for arranging my menu bar, especially with that notch on Macbook pro. I use <a href="https://folivora.ai/">Better Touch Tool</a> to assign taps to clicks (for example three finger tap to open in a new tab). I also use it to assign hyperkey. Hyperkey is when you press all meta keys together on the keyboard. For example, Hyperkey+A is my shortcut for quick task in Todoist. I use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/id1662213547">WeatherX</a> to have weather of 4 cities be readily accessible in the menu bar. I use <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/command-x/id6448461551">Command+X</a> to have a cut option in MacOS.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>AI Chat Interfaces</strong>: I use <a href="https://boltai.app/">Bolt AI</a> at the moment to organize my conversations, especially those that need to go through API for non-training purposes. There are 100 such apps, this is the one I found the earliest. If I do end up paying for <a href="https://www.raycast.com/pro">Raycast Pro</a>, then I would not need this app. I use Bolt because, it does not show up in dock, allows to select models per chat, allows to set shortcut to bring it up. I sometimes use <a href="https://chatgpt-sidebar.com/">Sider</a> (on browser) and <a href="https://www.macgpt.com/">MacGPT</a> (quick question - synonym for X) too.</p></li>
</ul>


</section>

<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>Tools</category>
  <category>MacOS</category>
  <category>Softwares</category>
  <guid>https://mimansajaiswal.github.io/personal_notes/mac_softwares.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
